Solidarity Committee of the Capital District; Records apap042
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1978-2000; 3; 13.8 cubic ft.
  - Asia, 1995-1996 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Asner, Ed, Correspondence, 1982; 1985; 1986 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - AT&T Strike, Communication Workers of America, 1986 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - BASF Strike, Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers, Local 4-620, 1985-1986 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Blueprint for Social Justice, 1990-1993 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, Strike against Maine Central Railroad and Guilford Railroad, 1986-1989 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Capital District Coalition Against Apartheid and Racism, 1985 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Capital District Farmers' Market Association, Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Capital District Labor-Religion Coalition, 1983; 1987 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Caravan Performance, Albany, 1988 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Cargill Strike, American Federation of Grain Miller, Local 540, 1984-1986 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - CAT Workers, Caterpillar, 1992 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Cement Workers, 1988; 1990 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Central Federation of Labor, Albany County, 1990 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Chinese Staff and Workers Association, 1992; 1994-1995 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Civil Service Employee Association (CSEA), 1984-1989 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Coalition for Labor Reform, 1993-1994 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Coalition for Social and Economic Justice, 1990-1992 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Coca Cola, Guatemala, 1984 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Colt Industries Strike, United Auto Workers, 1986-1987 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Commissioners' Management and Leadership Seminar, Workshop Summary, 1991 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Commissioners' Management and Leadership Seminar, Employee Involvement Programs, 1991 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Commisioners' Managements and Leadership Seminar, Leadership/ Team Building Resource Manual, 1991 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Communication Workers of America, 1986-1987 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - The Communicator, 1999 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Community Referral Center, 1990-1991 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Con-Way Express Strike, Teamsters Local 294, 1990-1992 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Copper Strike, News Clippings and Donations, 1984-1985 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Corporate Welfare, IBM, 1995 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Corporate Welfare, Reports by New York State Senator Franz Leichter, 1995 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Coyne Textiles, Unite Local 66L, 1996 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Crestline, 1995 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Daily News Strike, 1990 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Debt Framers' Union, South Central India, 1985-1986 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Democratic Economy, 1991-1992 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Demoreau Vending, 1984 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Directory of Labor Union and Employee Organizations in New York State, 1994 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Displaced Homemakers, 1987 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Divestment Lobby Day, Albany, 1985 March 19 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Eastern Airlines Strike, 1989-1990 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Economic Development, 1982-1993 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Endicott Local 826, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Environment, The Adirondacks, 1992-1993 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Environment, "Altered Immune Status in Aluminum Reduction Plant Workers", 1989 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Environment, Building a Movement, 1990; 1991; 1995 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Environment, Citizens' Environmental Coalition, 1991-1993 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Environment, News Clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Environment, Conferences, 1991-1992 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Environment, "Draft Study for a Hudson Valley Greenway", 1990 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Environment, "Economic and Social Implication of Waste in US Agriculture and Food Sectors", 1990 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Environment, Greenpeace, 1990-1993 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Environment, Hazardous Materials, 1985-1993 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Environment, Legislation, 1990-1992 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Environment, Nationwide Environmental Groups' Information and Newsletters, 1992-1993 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Environment, "New York under a Cloud: The Need to prevent Toxic Chemical Accidents", 1989 (Box 9 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Environment, Sierra Club, 1990-1993 (Box 9 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Environment, "Waste Not: Garbage as an Economic Resource for the Northeast", 1991 (Box 9 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Fair Tax Committee, 1992; 1995 (Box 9 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Farmers, 1990-1992 (Box 9 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Farmers, 1993-1998 (Box 9 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - "Fighting the Wrong Wars: Assessing New York's Executive Budget in Economic, Social and Fiscal Context", 1998-1999 (Box 9 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Fiscal Policy Institute, 1995 (Box 9 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Fleet Workers, 1996 (Box 9 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Food Pantries in the Capital District, Undated (Box 9 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Fulton County Economic Development, 1988-1989 (Box 10 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Furniture Workers, 1994 (Box 10 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - General Electric, 1991-1992 (Box 10 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Glove Workers' Strikes, 1984-1988 (Box 10 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Greenway Testimony, 1990 October 10 (Box 10 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Greyhound Strike, 1983 (Box 10 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Greyhound Strike, 1982 December-1984 April (Box 10 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Greyhound Strike, 1983-1984 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Greyhound Strike, 1986 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Greyhound Strike, Amalgamated Council of Greyhound Local Unions, 1990-1992 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Greyhound Strike, Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1202, 1990 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Greyhound Strike, Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1202, 1990 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Greyhound Strike, News Clippings, 1990-1993 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Greyhound Strike, Coresspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Greyhound Strike, Damage Reports, 1990 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Greyhound Strike, Flyers and Newsletter, 1990 (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Greyhound Strike, Greyhound Amalgamated Trusts, 1990 (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Greyhound Strike, Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Greyhound Strike, Vermont Transit Bus Drivers' Union, Undated (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Harness Horsemen's Association, 1993-1995 (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Health Care Project, 1985-1993 (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Health Care Project, 1985-1993 (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Health Issues, 1990-1999 (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Hormel Strike, United Food and Commercial Workers, Local P-199, 1987; Undated (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Housing, 1989-1990 (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Human Rights, 1988-1992 (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Human Rights, 1990-1992 (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Hunger Action Network of New York State, 1988-1993 (Box 13 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Immigration, 1991-1995 (Box 13 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Imperial Foods, Inc., Wanted Posters, 1991 (Box 13 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Indians, 1991-1993 (Box 13 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Industrial Development Agencies, 1995 (Box 13 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Injured Workers, 1989-1991 (Box 13 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - International Longshoremen's Association, Local 333, Port of Albany, 1988-1989 (Box 13 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - International Longshoremen's Association, Local 333, Port of Albany, 1988-1989 (Box 13 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Ironworkers Local 534, Menands Lockout, 1985-1989 (Box 13 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - The Island, Yearbook, 1923-1988 (Box 13 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - IUE Local 301 History, 1985-1987 (Box 13 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - James Bay II, Aluminire Alouette et. al. versus Commission d'Accs l'Information et. al, 1991 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - James Bay II, Arctic Circle, 1990-1991 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - James Bay II, Audubon, 1990-1991 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - James Bay II, Ban the Dam Jam, 1991 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - James Bay II, "The Buck Stops Here?", 1994 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - James Bay II, News Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - James Bay II, News Clippings, 1991 January-1991 June (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - James Bay II, News Clippings, 1991 July-1991 December (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - James Bay II, News Clippings, 1992 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - James Bay II, News Clippings, 1993-1995 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - James Bay II, Comments on Issues to be addressed in the New York State Energy Planning Report, 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - James Bay II, Conseil Central de Montreal, 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - James Bay II, Contract between Hydro-Quebec and Norsk Hydro Canada, Undated (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - James Bay II, Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - James Bay II, Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - James Bay II, Cree Regional Authority Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - James Bay II, Cree Regional Authority, 1991-1994 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - James Bay II, The CSN and the Great Whale Project, 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - James Bay II, Damming the Rivers of James Bay: Folly of the Century, Undated (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - James Bay II, "Draft Guidelines for the Environment Impact Study of the Great Whale Hydroelectric Project", 1992 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - James Bay II, "Electricity Conservation in the Northwest: A Hindrance or a Help to Economic Development", 1992 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - James Bay II, "Employment Effects of Electricity Conservation: The Case of British Columbia", 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - James Bay II, "Employment Impacts of Energy Development in New York State: Draft", 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - James Bay II, "Employment Impacts of New York State Energy Options", 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - James Bay II, "Energy Development in the Quebec Context", 1989-1993 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - James Bay II, "Everything You Wanted to Know about Power Smart", 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - James Bay II, Fact Sheets on Hydro-Quebec's James Bay II Project, Undated (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - James Bay II, Flyers and Pamphlets, Undated (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - James Bay II, Friedlander, Miriam, 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - James Bay II "Gambling for Gigabucks", 1986 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - James Bay II, "Guidelines for the Environment Impact Statement for the Proposed Great Whale River Hydroelectric Project", 1992 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - James Bay II, Innu Nation, 1992 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - James Bay II, Action Network, Undated (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - James Bay II, James Bay Activists, 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - James Bay II, "The James Bay Power Project: The Environmental Cost of Reshaping the Geography of Northern Quebec", Undated (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - James Bay II, James Bay Defense Coalition, 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - James Bay II, James Bay Publication Series, 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - James Bay II, Maps, 1989 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - James Bay II, Memo Regarding Research on "Programme de Partage de Risques et Benefices", 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - James Bay II, Miscellaneous, 1991; Undated (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - James Bay II, Moynihan, Daniel P., 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - James Bay II, "Megawatts: A Practical Remedy for Megagoofs", 1985 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - James Bay II, Newsletters, 1990-1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - James Bay II, New York City Department of Telecommunications and Energy, 1991 July (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - James Bay II, New York State Assembly, 1990-1992 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - James Bay II, New York State Energy Office, 1992 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - James Bay II, "New York's Revised Long-Run Avoided Costs and the Impact of the 800MW Hydro-Quebec/NYPA Contract", Undated (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - James Bay II, "New York's Role in James Bay", 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - James Bay II, NE Alliance to Protect James Bay, 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - James Bay II, NE Regional James Bay Action Conference, 1991 October 4-6 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - James Bay II, Prudent Residents Opposed To Electric Cable Transmission (PROTECT), 1990-1993 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - James Bay II, Protected Economic Impact of the Revised Energy Sections of the State Building Code, 1987 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - James Bay II, Publication Catalog, American Council for and Energy-Efficient Economy, 1990 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - James Bay II, Resolutions, Statements, and Testimonies, 1991-1992 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - James Bay II, Sierra Club, 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - James Bay II, Student Environmental Action Coalition (SEAC), 1991 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - James Bay II, Transcripts of Oral Comment, Hearing, 1990 September 17 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - James Bay II, Utility Workers Union of America, 1990 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Jobs with Justice, 1994-1999 (Box 16 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Jobs with Justice, I'll Be There, 1996-1999 (Box 16 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Joint Labor/ Management Relations Workshop, Participant Manual, 1991 (Box 16 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - "Just Cause", Undated (Box 16 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Labor Day Celebrations, 1984-1985 (Box 16 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Labor Day Celebrations, 1986-1987; 1989-1991; 1997-1998; 2000; 2002 (Box 16 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Labor Day Celebrations, 1999-2000 (Box 17 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Labor Day, Press Reactions, 1983 (Box 17 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Labor Law, 1991-1992 (Box 17 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Labor Notes, 1990-1993 (Box 17 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Labor Notes, Team Concept School, 1991 (Box 17 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Labor Songs, Undated (Box 17 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Latin America, 1985-1988 (Box 17 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Latin America, 1989-1996 (Box 17 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Latin America, El Salvador, 1989-1995 (Box 18 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Latin America, Guatemala, 1991-1995 (Box 18 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Latin America, Haiti, 1997 (Box 18 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Latin America, Mexico, 1989-1997 (Box 18 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Latin America, National Labor Committee, Education Fund Support of Worker and Human Rights in Central America, 1995-1998 (Box 18 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Latin America, Nicaragua, 1992 (Box 18 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Latin America, US/Guatemala Labor Education Project, 1992-1997 (Box 18 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Laundry Workers Strike, Stillwater, 1984-1985 (Box 18 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Legal Services Staff Association, 1991-1992 (Box 18 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Living Wage Campaign, 1997-1998 (Box 18 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - May Day Dinners, 1986; 1999; 2009 (Box 18 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Mexican Workers in Albany, 1994-1996 (Box 18 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Military, 1990 (Box 18 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Minimum Wage, 1988 (Box 19 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Minimum Wage, 1993 (Box 19 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Minimum Wage, 1994 (Box 19 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Minimum Wage, 1995 (Box 19 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Minimum Wage, 1996-1997 (Box 19 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Minimum Wage, Campaign for Living Minimum Wage, 1996 (Box 19 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Minimum Wage, News Clippings, 1985-1992 (Box 19 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Minimum Wage, News Clippings, 1993 (Box 19 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Minimum Wage, News Clippings, 1994 (Box 19 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Minimum Wage, News Clippings, 1995 (Box 19 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Minimum Wage, News Clippings, 1996-1997 (Box 20 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Minimum Wage, Correspondence, Incoming, 1993-1995 (Box 20 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Minimum Wage, Correspondence, Outgoing, 1991-1995 (Box 20 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Minimum Wage, Earned Income Credit, 1993-1994 (Box 20 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Minimum Wage, Leaflets, 1994-1995 (Box 20 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Minimum Wage, Mailing Lists, Undated (Box 20 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Minimum Wage, Maximum Wage Information, 1995 (Box 20 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Minimum Wage, Meeting Notes and Minutes, 1994 (Box 20 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Minimum Wage, Miscellaneous, 1993-1995 (Box 20 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Minimum Wage, New York State Department of Labor, 1993-1995 (Box 20 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Minimum Wage, New York State Labor Law, 1979-1991 (Box 20 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Minimum Wage, Papers by Fred Pfeiffer, 1994-1995 (Box 20 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Minimum Wage, Petitions, 1994-1997 (Box 20 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Minimum Wage, Press Releases, 1993-1995 (Box 20 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Minimum Wage, Prevailing Rate Schedules, Undated (Box 20 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Minimum Wage, Public Hearing, 1995 March 21 (Box 20 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Minimum Wage, Reports, 1994 (Box 21 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Minimum Wage, Reports and Studies, 1993-1995 (Box 21 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Minimum Wage, Resolutions, 1993 (Box 21 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Minimum Wage, Teach In, 1995 February 16 (Box 21 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Minimum Wage, Undated (Box 21 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, Pamphlets, General Activism, Undated (Box 21 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, Correspondence, Undated (Box 21 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, Newsletters, Undated (Box 22 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, Newsletters, Undated (Box 22 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Newsletters and News Clippings, Undated (Box 22 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - National Jobs for All Coalition, 1999 (Box 22 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - The Neighborhood Works, 1998 (Box 22 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Guild, Local 34, 1985-1988 (Box 22 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - New Yorkers for Fiscal Fairness, 1998 (Box 22 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - New York State Assembly, 1989-1999 (Box 22 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - New York State Capital Labor Parade, 1999 (Box 23 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, 1997-1998 (Box 23 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - New York State Department of Economic Development Capital Region Resource Manual, 1991 (Box 23 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - New York State Department of Economic Development Capital Region Resource Manual, 1991 (Box 23 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - New York State Farm Alliance, 1986-1989 (Box 23 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - New York State King Community Service Initiative, 1998 (Box 23 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - New York State Labor Party, 1996-1998 (Box 23 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - New York State Labor Party, Capital District and Metro Chapters, 1997-1999 (Box 23 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - New York State Labor Party, Education Conference, 1998-1999 (Box 23 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - New York State Labor -Religion Coalition and New York State Interfaith Impact, 1991-1995 (Box 23 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - New York State Legislative Workers, 1995 (Box 23 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - "New York's Persistent Energy Crisis: The Consequences of Overuse and the Availability of Power through Energy Efficiency", Undated (Box 24 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - New York Solidarity, Pyramid Lake, 1991-1994 (Box 24 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Nonviolence, 1989-1991 (Box 24 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - North America Free Trade Agreement, 1992-1993 (Box 24 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - North America Free Trade Agreement, 1992-1993 (Box 24 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - North America Free Trade Agreement, 1994-1999 (Box 25 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - North America Free Trade Agreement, Undated (Box 25 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Nuclear Testing Bans, 1984-1988 (Box 25 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Nurses, Visiting Nurses, 1985 (Box 25 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Nurses, Seton Nurses, 1998 (Box 25 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Nurses' Strike, Local 1199, Port Jervis, NY, 1994-1994 (Box 25 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Occupational Safety and Health Administration, 1993-1995 (Box 25 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Pittston Coal Strike, 1989 (Box 25 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Plant Closings and Lay-off Moratorium, 1987 (Box 25 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Plattsburgh Local 788, 1991 (Box 25 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Portec Strike, United Steel Workers of America, Local 8652, 1986-1987 (Box 25 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Price Chopper, 1991 (Box 25 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Privatization, 1989-1992 (Box 25 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Professional Air Traffic Controllers Strike, 1981-1982 (Box 26 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Public Citizen, 1998 (Box 26 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Public Employees Federation, 1984-1985; 1999 (Box 26 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Public Employees Federation, Policy Manual, 1994 (Box 26 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Public Employees Federation, Policy Manual, 1994 (Box 26 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - "Race in the Workplace: Is Affirmative Action Working?", 1991 (Box 26 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Ravenswood Lockout, West Virginia, 1991-1992 (Box 26 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Rhode Island, 1995 (Box 26 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - St. Anne's Institute Organizing, Albany, NY, 1985 (Box 26 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)